---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://critterism-be.herokuapp.com/api/v1/trivia
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      User-Agent:
      - Faraday v2.6.0
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - Cowboy
      Date:
      - Wed, 09 Nov 2022 16:11:55 GMT
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      Content-Type:
      - application/json; charset=utf-8
      Etag:
      - W/"e55d628158a3f77dc114caf8bdb581e9"
      Cache-Control:
      - max-age=0, private, must-revalidate
      X-Request-Id:
      - b36bdc44-1366-44df-98ff-cf884336d602
      X-Runtime:
      - '0.039533'
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Via:
      - 1.1 vegur
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"data":[{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The
        Ceratosaurus, a dinosaur known for having a horn on the top of its nose, is
        also known to be a decendent of the Tyrannosaurus Rex.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"],"answers":["True","False"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Cashmere
        is the wool from which kind of animal?","correct_answer":"Goat","incorrect_answers":["Sheep","Camel","Llama"],"answers":["Sheep","Camel","Llama","Goat"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the scientific name for the \u0026quot;Polar Bear\u0026quot;?","correct_answer":"Ursus
        Maritimus","incorrect_answers":["Polar Bear","Ursus Spelaeus","Ursus Arctos"],"answers":["Polar
        Bear","Ursus Spelaeus","Ursus Arctos","Ursus Maritimus"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        scientific suborder does the family Hyaenidae belong to?","correct_answer":"Feliformia","incorrect_answers":["Haplorhini","Caniformia","Ciconiiformes"],"answers":["Haplorhini","Caniformia","Ciconiiformes","Feliformia"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        is the scientific name of the Budgerigar?","correct_answer":"Melopsittacus
        undulatus","incorrect_answers":["Nymphicus hollandicus","Pyrrhura molinae","Ara
        macao"],"answers":["Nymphicus hollandicus","Pyrrhura molinae","Ara macao","Melopsittacus
        undulatus"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        type of creature is a Bonobo?","correct_answer":"Ape","incorrect_answers":["Lion","Parrot","Wildcat"],"answers":["Lion","Parrot","Wildcat","Ape"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which
        of these species is not extinct?","correct_answer":"Komodo dragon","incorrect_answers":["Japanese
        sea lion","Tasmanian tiger","Saudi gazelle"],"answers":["Japanese sea lion","Tasmanian
        tiger","Saudi gazelle","Komodo dragon"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"The
        dish Fugu, is made from what family of fish?","correct_answer":"Pufferfish","incorrect_answers":["Bass","Salmon","Mackerel"],"answers":["Bass","Salmon","Mackerel","Pufferfish"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the scientific name of the Common Chimpanzee?","correct_answer":"Pan troglodytes","incorrect_answers":["Gorilla
        gorilla","Pan paniscus","Panthera leo"],"answers":["Gorilla gorilla","Pan
        paniscus","Panthera leo","Pan troglodytes"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"You
        can tell the age of a ladybird by counting the spots on his back.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"],"answers":["True","False"]}}]}'
  recorded_at: Wed, 09 Nov 2022 16:11:55 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
